Guide to the Allen Ginsberg film and video archive, 1983 - 1996
Department of Special Collections
- Kerouac, Part II. (Box 3, Folder 25)
  A documentary by John Antonelli 1984, with actors playing all the main Beat historical figures. An interesting combination of narrative and documentary filmmaking.
  - Allen Ginsberg interview.
    Time in: 0:08:29 Time out: 0:09:09 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg on Kerouac's drinking before his appearance on the 1969 William Buckley show.
  - Kerouac on Firing Line, the William Buckley PBS show, 1969.
    Time in: 0:09:35 Time out: 0:10:14 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg appears in the audience. Kerouac expresses his negative attitude towards the Beats.
  - Allen Ginsberg interview.
    Time in: 0:11:15 Time out: 0:11:51 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg on Kerouac, Catholicism and suffering.
  - Allen Ginsberg interview.
    Time in: 0:14:50 Time out: 0:15:43 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg states that Kerouac had a heart and mind that could write about the real world.
- Peter Orlovsky and Allen Ginsberg. (Box 3, Folder 26)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:51:41 Total Time: 41m 33s Source: 3/4" Master unusable Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Color video of Ginsberg and Orlovsky in 1978, performing with Jack Allan Cassady. Quality of this video is almost unusable except for the sound.
- USA: Poetry: Outtakes. (Box 3, Folder 27)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:55:12 Total Time: 55m 12s Source: B/W Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Outtakes from a 1965 episode of USA: Poetry series for WNET. Directed by Richard Moore. Video transfer quality is questionable.
  - Ginsberg interview in the basement of City Lights book store, San Francisco, July 18, 1965.
    Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:09:28 Source: B/W Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg talks about poetry and reads some poems.
  - Robert Creeley and Neal Cassady enter the scene and sit down to watch.
    Time in: 0:09:28 Time out: 0:14:50 Source: B/W Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg reads "King of May".
  - More poetry and general discussion.
    Time in: 0:14:55 Time out: 0:27:00 Source: B/W Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg and Cassady discuss the world situation.
  - Ginsberg talks about William Carlos Williams and other poets.
    Time in: 0:27:02 Time out: 0:31:14 Source: B/W Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    This section ends the basement of City Lights interview.
  - Ginsberg's apartment in San Francisco, December 14, 1965.
    Time in: 0:31:15 Time out: 0:38:31 Source: B/W Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    General hustle and bustle in apartment with Ginsberg, Julius and Peter Orlovsky and Neal Cassady.
  - Everyone leaves the apartment and boards a VW bus.
    Time in: 0:38:31 Time out: 0:41:09 Source: B/W Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Interesting shots of everyone in a VW bus.
  - Studio of artist, Robert LaVigne, San Francisco.
    Time in: 0:41:10 Time out: 0:44:35 Source: B/W Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg stands in front of Robert's painting: Foster's Cafeteria.
  - Ginsberg and Orlovksy perform a musical mantra in the studio.
    Time in: 0:44:36 Time out: 0:47:40 Source: B/W Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Orlovsky plays guitar and Ginsberg chimes a small bell.
  - Ginsberg in studio while LaVigne paints.
    Time in: 0:47:40 Time out: 0:55:07 Source: B/W Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg reads poems and explains them.
- Buddha Bellies; September on Jessore Road. (Box 3, Folder 28)
  Time in: 5:02:13 Time out: 5:26:08 Total Time: 23m 55s Source: B/W Film & Color Film Prints Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Two short films featuring Ginsberg and his work.
  - Buddha Bellies.
    Time in: 5:02:13 Time out: 5:10:06 Total Time: 7m 53s Source: B/W Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Peter Orlovsky and Ginsberg in a film by Sheila and Lucien Carr.
  - Outtakes from Buddha Bellies.
    Time in: 5:10:20 Time out: 5:16:25 Total Time: 6m 5s Source: B/W Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Footage of Orlovsky and Ginsberg not included in Buddha Bellies.
  - September on Jessore Road.
    Time in: 5:16:40 Time out: 5:26:08 Total Time: 9m 28s Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    A film by John Giorno depicts Allen in India, including song "Jessore Road" with Bob Dylan playing in back-up band.
- Excerpts from Good Morning Mr. Orwell. (Box 3, Folder 29)
  Time in: 0:47:20 Time out: 0:55:30 Total Time: 7m 52s Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  A TV special that aired New Year's Eve, 1983, featuring multi-media performances.
  - "Do the Meditation Rock".
    Time in: 0:47:20 Time out: 0:50:00 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Relatively good version of this particular poem/chant.
  - Allen Ginsberg and Peter Orlovsky singing (over closing credits).
    Time in: 0:53:50 Time out: 0:55:30 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Closes program.
- Pull My Daisy; Allan 'n' Allen's Complaint. (Box 3, Folder 30)
  Time in: 7:00:27 Time out: 7:56:21 Total Time: 55m 54s Source: Film and Video Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Pull My Daisy by Robert Frank. Allan 'n' Allen's Complaint by Nam June Paik.
  - Pull My Daisy.
    Time in: 7:00:27 Time out: 7:27:27 Total Time: 27m 0s Source: B/W Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    A short film by Robert Frank and Alfred Leslie in 1958. Written and narrated by Jack Kerouac, with Allen Ginsberg, Gregory Corso, Peter Orlovsky, Larry Rivers, David Amram and others.
  - Allan 'n' Allen's Complaint.
    Time in: 7:27:48 Time out: 7:56:21 Total Time: 28m 30s Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Video art piece by Nam June Paik and Shiseko Kubota in 1982.
  - Allan 'n' Allen's Complaint: Opening.
    Time in: 7:27:48 Time out: 7:32:24 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Experimental video images with distorted sound.
  - Allan 'n' Allen's Complaint: Allen Ginsberg and his father, Louis Ginsberg, in joint poetry reading, 1975.
    Time in: 7:32:25 Time out: 7:36:01 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Footage of Allen and Louis Ginsberg reading together.
  - Allan 'n' Allen's Complaint: Peter Orlovsky, Boulder CO.
    Time in: 7:40:22 Time out: 7:40:55 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Orlovsky is playing the banjo on the Boulder mall.
  - Allan 'n' Allen's Complaint: Allen Ginsberg and his father 3 years after Louis Ginsberg's death, images combined by video.
    Time in: 7:40:56 Time out: 7:42:08 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    A video image of Louis is superimposed onto Allen's forehead. Allen is crying.
  - Allan 'n' Allen's Complaint: Superimposed images of Allen Ginsberg and Peter Orlovsky.
    Time in: 7:42:09 Time out: 7:42:24 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Experimental imagery and sound.
  - Allan 'n' Allen's Complaint: Orlovsky playing banjo -- Boulder. Interview with Allen Ginsberg and Allan Kaprow.
    Time in: 7:47:49 Time out: 7:52:25 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg explains what it was like coming out to his father and how difficult it was.
  - Allan 'n' Allen's Complaint: Allen and Louis Ginsberg.
    Time in: 7:55:10 Time out: 7:56:21 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
- Ginsberg and Orlovsky; Ginsberg and Student; Ginsberg and Gregory Corso (Box 4, Folder 31)
  Time in: 23:02:02 Time out: 12:57:02 Total Time: 33m 35s Source: Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Ginsberg playing music with Peter Orlovsky, teaches a Naropa student, and discusses the past with Gregory Corso.
  - Ginsberg and Orlovsky
    Time in: 23:02:02 Time out: 23:04:22 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg and Peter Orlovsky singing together. Peter is playing the banjo.
  - Ginsberg and Naropa Student
    Time in: 12:10:51 Time out: 12:16:30 Source: 16mm Negative Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Picture only. Ginsberg and student discuss poetry on the lawn in front of Ginsberg's Boulder home.
  - Ginsberg and Naropa Student
    Time in: 12:24:04 Time out: 12:35:49 Source: 16mm Work Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Picture and sound, picture scratched. Ginsberg and student discuss poetry on the lawn in front of Ginsberg's Boulder home.
  - Allen Ginsberg and Gregory Corso talking.
    Time in: 12:44:13 Time out: 12:46:51 Source: 16 mm Work Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg and Corso dispute the details of an early poetry reading. Corso reflects on Neal Cassady and success with women.
  - Allen Ginsberg and Gregory Corso talking.
    Time in: 12:54:28 Time out: 12:57:02 Source: 16 mm Work Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg and Corso discuss Kerouac and Cassady in the early days. Corso comments on finding out about Ginsberg's homosexuality. (Picture out at 12:56:50)
- Allen and Louis Ginsberg Part I. (Box 4, Folder 32)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:42:38 Total Time: 42m 38s Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Father and son poets read together for an audience, 1973.
- Allen and Louis Ginsberg, Part II. (Box 4, Folder 33)
  Time in: 2:00:00 Time out: 2:27:13 Total Time: 27m 13s Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
- Be In; America's Wonderful. (Box 4, Folder 34)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:14:18 Total Time: 14m 25s Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Two short films: Be In by Jerry Abrams, and America's Wonderful by John Giorgio, both from 1967.
  - Be In
    Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:07:10 Total Time: 7m 10s Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Celebration of life in Golden Gate Park, San Francisco.
  - Be In: Footage of Ginsberg in the 60's, reading poetry at a concert.
    Time in: 0:01:55 Time out: 0:05:30 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  - Be In: Ginsberg dancing.
    Time in: 0:05:50 Time out: 0:05:55 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  - Be In: Ginsberg on stage.
    Time in: 0:07:00 Time out: 0:07:10 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  - America's Wonderful: Footage of Ginsberg in the 60's, reading poetry at a concert.
    Time in: 0:08:30 Time out: 0:09:25 Total Time: 7m 04s Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
- In Motion: Amiri Baraka. (Box 4, Folder 35)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:59:08 Total Time: 59m 08s Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  Biographical film of poet Leroi Jones, also known as Amiri Baraka, by St. Claire Bourne, 1981.
  - Ginsberg interviewed with a book of poetry.
    Time in: 0:05:25 Time out: 0:06:55 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg discusses his long friendship with Baraka.
  - Ginsberg on a trip to Washington, Howard University, reading Baraka's poems.
    Time in: 0:08:20 Time out: 0:10:15 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    They share a strong mutual respect for each other's politics and poetry.
  - Ginsberg on Baraka, Fascism in Newark.
    Time in: 0:49:30 Time out: 0:51:00 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Baraka explains how Ginsberg, through "Howl", turned him on to his own anger as a black man in America.
- Burroughs, Part I. (Box 4, Folder 36)
  Time in: 0:01:00 Time out: 1:01:38 Total Time: 61m 38s Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  The definitive 1984 documentary on the life of William Burroughs by Howard Brookner (deceased).
  - Ginsberg interview.
    Time in: 0:04:00 Time out: 0:04:15 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg on Burroughs.
  - Burroughs interview.
    Time in: 0:19:10 Time out: 0:19:30 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Burroughs on meeting Ginsberg and the other Beats in 1944.
  - Terry Southern interview.
    Time in: 0.19.30 Time out: 0:19:40 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Terry Southern telling how Kerouac and Ginsberg referred to Burroughs as "Daddy".
  - Ginsberg and Burroughs together.
    Time in: 0:20:10 Time out: 0:23:30 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg and Burroughs together on NYC rooftop, reciting "Howl".
  - Ginsberg and Lucien Carr with Burroughs.
    Time in: 0:23:30 Time out: 0:25:30 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Discussing relationships.
  - Ginsberg interview.
    Time in: 0:28:05 Time out: 0:28:30 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg on Burroughs forging prescriptions.
  - Ginsberg and Burroughs.
    Time in: 0:55:20 Time out: 0:55:40 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
- Burroughs, Part II. (Box 4, Folder 37)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:29:12 Total Time: 29m 12s Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  - Ginsberg interview.
    Time in: 0:00:30 Time out: 0:03:00 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg on the relationship between Burroughs and his son.
  - Ginsberg interview.
    Time in: 0:06:55 Time out: 0:07:25 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg on Burroughs' writing.
- Suwanose: The Fourth World. (Box 4, Folder 38)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 1.03:02 Total Time: 63m 2s Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  A television program from 1976 about the protest surrounding the aboriginal peoples on the small Japanese island Suwanose.
  - Allen at Berkeley poetry reading reciting "Save Suwanose".
    Time in: 0:49:50 Time out: 0:55:09 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Allen on stage with other poets, both American and Japanese.
  - "Put Down Your Cigarette Rag (Don't Smoke)"
    Time in: 0:55:10 Time out: 0:59:20 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg sings over footage of Japanese protesters dancing.
  - Caricature drawing of Allen.
    Time in: 1:00:00 Time out: 1:00:05 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Caricature drawing of Ginsberg appears with Japanese titles.
  - Allen chanting.
    Time in: 1:00:10 Time out: 1:00:40 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    As the program closes, Ginsberg sings a mantra with other poets on stage.
- Spectrum: "Anatomy of Violence". (Box 4, Folder 39)
  Time in: 0:00:00 Time out: 0:28:36 Total Time: 28m 36s Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  A sociological study of violence using footage from the "Dialectics of Liberation" convention in London, 1967.
  - Ginsberg speaking on the panel.
    Time in: 0:02:07 Time out: 0:02:18 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg advocating non-escalation as a resolution to violence.
  - About Ginsberg.
    Time in: 0:02:31 Time out: 0:02:37 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg described as "poet-prophet of the flower people."
  - Ginsberg speaking on a panel.
    Time in: 0:09:41 Time out: 0:09:55 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg argues that domestic interracial violence does not help curtail the Vietnam war.
  - Ginsberg and Stokely Carmichael.
    Time in: 0:10:01 Time out: 0:10:12 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg and Carmichael shown together on the panel.
  - Ginsberg speaking on a panel.
    Time in: 0:12:30 Time out: 0:14:04 Source: Color Film Print Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg on "flower power strategies."
  - Yippie press conference, including: Allen Ginsberg, Ed Sanders, Judy Collins and Paul Krassner.
    Time in: 0:06:30 Time out: 0:08:09 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    A series of famous people of the times address the press about the alternative convention of life to be held in Chicago during the 1968 Democratic Convention.
  - Allen Ginsberg addresses the U.S. Congress.
    Time in: 0:08:12 Time out: 0:09:11 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg speaks to the LSD Committee on the value of LSD, June 14, 1966.
  - Allen Ginsberg and William Burroughs in Chicago.
    Time in: 0:09:16 Time out: 0:11:02 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg and Burroughs in the crowd hold flowers and look anxious (silent footage).
  - Allen Ginsberg.
    Time in: 0:11:05 Time out: 0:12:34 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg at a Canadian demonstration, (silent footage).
  - Allen Ginsberg and Pete Seeger.
    Time in: 0:12:52 Time out: 0:14:51 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg speaks and Seeger sings at an anti-war tax-evasion rally in 1967.
  - 1968 Republican Convention.
    Time in: 0:15:06 Time out: 0:23:41 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    The contest between Rockefeller, Regan and Nixon. There is a great celebration when Nixon wins.
  - Vietnam.
    Time in: 0:23:42 Time out: 0:23:56 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Gruesome footage of American and Vietnamese causalities, 1967.
  - Chicago and Hubert Humphry.
    Time in: 0:24:10 Time out: 0:31:32 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    This footage contains shots of rioting in the streets of Chicago juxtaposed with Humphry winning the Democratic Convention, also in Chicago.
- St. Cloud College Footage. (Box 4, Folder 40)
  Time in: 3:00:24 Time out: 0:15:10 Total Time: 15m 10s Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  A short black and white film about Allen Ginsberg visiting St. Cloud State University, Minnesota, 1976. Includes Ginsberg interview footage.
  - St. Cloud College Footage.
    Time in: 3:00:24 Time out: 3:08:22 Total Time: 7m 58s Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    A short black and white piece by Michael F. Cassidy and Richard Reeder chronicling Ginsberg's visit to St. Cloud College sometime in the mid-1960's.
  - St. Cloud College Footage: Allen Ginsberg singing.
    Time in: 3:00:24 Time out: 3:01:52 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Allen Ginsberg sings "Can't Find Anyone" over images of Ginsberg arriving at St. Cloud College.
  - St. Cloud College Footage: Allen Ginsberg chanting.
    Time in: 3:01:54 Time out: 0:02:16 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Footage of Ginsberg chanting.
  - St. Cloud College Footage: Allen Ginsberg interview.
    Time in: 3.02.17 Time out: 3:03:14 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg discusses being a writer and seeing like a writer.
  - St. Cloud College Footage: Allen Ginsberg interview.
    Time in: 3:03:25 Time out: 3:04:19 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg comments on Buddhist meditation and poetry and observing thought forms. We see visuals of Ginsberg meditating and lecturing over his comments.
  - St. Cloud College Footage: Interview with Allen Ginsberg
    Time in: 3:04:20 Time out: 3:04:32 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg remarks on how the urge to cling to the material world is the source of all pain.
  - St. Cloud College Footage: Chanting sequence.
    Time in: 3:04:33 Time out: 3:05:37 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    We hear Ginsberg chanting over still photos of Ginsberg.
  - St. Cloud College Footage: Allen Ginsberg singing.
    Time in: 3:05:38 Time out: 3:06:12 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg sings "Broken Bones" over images of him visiting the college bookstore and signing books.
  - St. Cloud College Footage: Allen Ginsberg singing.
    Time in: 3:06:13 Time out: 3:07:17 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg sings live before an audience.
  - St. Cloud College Footage: Interview with Allen Ginsberg.
    Time in: 3:07:19 Time out: 3:08:06 Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
    Ginsberg comments on writing poetry. Also, on the audio track, a group of people sing "Happy Birthday" to Ginsberg.
- I Believe: Allen Ginsberg. (Box 5, Folder 41)
  Time in: 4:00:44 Time out: 4:29:30 Total Time: 27m 46s Source: 3/4" Master Screening Format: 3/4" Window Dub Dubbing format: Beta Dub Master
  An episode of the KPIX-TV San Francisco television series I Believe, featuring Allen Ginsberg being interviewed by Father Miles Riley, 1974.
  - Allen Ginsberg reading poetry.